<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Dastan Games Studio</title>
    <link>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Dastan Games Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Light Inside Us</title>
      <link>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>The Light Inside Us&amp;rsquo; lead protagonist is made up of the Children of Light. A collection of many smaller particles that you must guide through a stylistically rendered isometric world.
Within this world, players must then defend themselves against wave upon wave of enemies, doing so by using the particles themselves as weapons.
For each shot taken you&amp;rsquo;ll lose a part of your life, but equally for every enemy you defeat you’ll grow ever stronger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps &amp; Dragons</title>
      <link>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Trick your friend into falling into devious traps. Use hints to choose the best steps, run to the top, discover hidden dragons and be the first to find the magic scroll in this mystical land of monks! Do you know your friends well enough? Find out in a game of Steps &amp;amp; Dragons!
Features:
Real-time online multiplayer for 2 players. Single-player daily challenge mode Upgradable and powerful spell cards Play Store </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rope Ball</title>
      <link>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>Touch the platforms to hold on to them and maneuver to reach the basket.
Play Store </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Heroes: Warrior Princess</title>
      <link>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Challenging puzzle game featuring cute voxel art, set in medieval times!
30 Handcrafted levels Increasingly challenging mechanics every few levels Cure voxel art style The King and Princess of Samaria set out for a peaceful picnic in the forest. While the king slept, they were suddenly beset by Goblins! The Princess must protect her father from these creatures before they attack him in his sleep!
The Goblins and the Princess move one step at a time and it&amp;rsquo;s upto the Princess to cut them off and destroy them before they reach the king!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match &amp; Patch</title>
      <link>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dastangamesstudio.github.io/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>The road is riddled with potholes. Help this family to reach their destination by repairing the roads.
Slide the blocks to combine them with other blocks.
Form a shape to match the hole and slide to fill it. Nothing is more relaxing than a smooth ride!
Play Store </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
